A Guide to The University of Virginia Hospital Auxiliary Collection 1908-2014
Claude Moore Health Sciences Library
- MINUTES, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1991 (June 1) - 1992 (May), TMs (Box-folder 016-006)
  Max Gentry
- MINUTES AND AMENDED BYLAWS UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1992 (June 16) - 1993 (April 15), TMs (Box-folder 016-007)
  Max Gentry; Contains amended bylaws
- MINUTES, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1993 (June 17) - 1994 (May 26), TMs (Box-folder 016-008)
  Carolina Fox
- MINUTES, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1994 (June 16) - 1995 (March 16), TMs (Box-folder 016-009)
  Carolina Fox; Contains Link, Volume 7, Number 3, February 27, 1995
- MINUTES, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1994 (May 26) - 1995 (June15), TMs (Box-folder 016-010)
  Carolina Fox, Scott Kammire
- MINUTES, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1995 (June 15) - 1996 (May 21), TMs (Box-folder 016-011)
  Scott Kammire
- MINUTES, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1996 (June 18) - 1997 (April 17), TMs (Box-folder 016-012)
- MINUTES, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1997 (April 17) - 1998 (May 20), TMs (Box-folder 017-001)
  Sue Pickett
- MINUTES, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1998 (June 16 - 1999 (May 20), TMs (Box-folder 017-002)
  Sue Pickett, Lucille Digges
- MINUTES, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 1999 (June 17) - 2000 (April 20), TMs (Box-folder 017-003)
  Lucille Digges
- MINUTES, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 2000 (September 21) - 2002 (May 22), TMs (Box-folder 017-004)
  Ann Sinarski
- MINUTES, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 2001 (June 21) - 2002 (May 22), TMs (Box-folder 017-005)
  Dorothy Richards
- MINUTES, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 2002 (June 20) - 2003 (May 15), TMs (Box-folder 017-006)
  Sandra Wagaman; Robert Campbell
- MINUTES, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 2003 (June 19) - 2004 (May 20), TMs (Box-folder 017-007)
  Robert Campbell
- MINUTES, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 2004 (June 17) - 2005 (May 26), TMs (Box-folder 017-008)
  Debbie Gardner, Kathy Quale
- MINUTES, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 2005 (June 16) - 2006 (June 1), TMs (Box-folder 017-009)
  Kathy Quale, Pat Periolat
- FINANCIAL STATEMENTS (BALANCE SHEETS UVA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY) 2006 (April-June), TMs (Box-folder 017-010)
- ANNUAL REPORT, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 2006 (June), TMs (Box-folder 017-011)
- MINUTES, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 2006 (June 16) - 2007 (May 24), TMs (Box-folder 017-012)
  Pat Periolat
- FINANCIAL STATEMENTS (BALANCE SHEETS UVA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY) 2006 (July) - 2007 (April), TMs (Box-folder 017-013)
- ANNUAL REPORT, UVA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 2007 (May), TMs (Box-folder 017-014)
- MINUTES, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 2007 (June 21) - 2008 (May 28), TMs (Box-folder 017-015)
  Pat Periolat, Lynda Dunn
- FINANCIAL STATEMENTS (BALANCE SHEETS UVA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY) 2007 (July) - 2008 [February], TMs (Box-folder 017-016)
- ANNUAL REPORT, UVA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 2008 (May), TMs (Box-folder 017-017)
- MINUTES, UVA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY (LYNDA DUNN) 2008 (June 19) - 2009 (April 19), TMs (Box-folder 017-018)
  Lynda Dunn
- FINANCIAL STATEMENTS (BALANCE SHEETS UVA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY) 2008 (July 31) - 2009 (April 30), TMs (Box-folder 017-019)
- SUBSTANTIVE BOARD OF DIRECTORS RESOLUTIONS UVA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY (BEGINNING MARCH 2000) 2009 March, 1 TMs (Box-folder 017-020)
- LETTER FROM LYNDA DUNN TO AUXILIANS RE: PROPOSED BY-LAW CHANGES (MAY 2009) 2009, April 20, 1 TL, 1 TD (Box-folder 017-021)
- ANNUAL REPORT, UVA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 2009 May, TMs (Box-folder 017-022)
- INVITATION TO LUNCHEON, AGENDA, AND 2009-2010 BUDGET FOR HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 2009 (May 21), 3 TD, 1 business card (Box-folder 017-023)
- UVA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY BOARD OF DIRECTORS MEETINGS MINUTES 2009 (June 19) - 2010 [May], TMs (Box-folder 017-024)
  The monthly minutes and those from the annual meeting in May (no meetings in August and December) include reports from various committe members and list the Board of Director officers and members. Martha Weiss
- UVA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY FINANCIAL POLICY 2010 (April 15), TMs (Box-folder 017-025)
  The policy supersedes prior policies.
- ANNUAL REPORT, UVA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 2010 May, TMs (Box-folder 017-026)
  "Volunteers Sow Seeds of Caring"
- UVA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY BOARD OF DIRECTORS MEETINGS MINUTES 2010 June 17 - 2011 May 25, TMs (Box-folder 018-001)
  The monthly minutes and those from the annual meeting in May (no meetings in August and December) include reports from various committe members. Meg Riechman
- UVA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY VENTURE AWARDS 2010, TMs (Box-folder 018-002)
- ANNUAL REPORT, UVA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 2011 May, TMs (Box-folder 018-003)
- UVA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY BOARD OF DIRECTORS MEETINGS MINUTES 2011 June 16 - 2012 May 24, TMs (Box-folder 018-004)
  President Maggie Van Winkle; also includes the Venture Awards in October minutes
- UVA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY BOARD OF DIRECTORS MEETINGS MINUTES 2012 June 21 - 2013 May 23, TMs (Box-folder 018-005)
  President Jane McLaughlin.
- UVA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY BOARD OF DIRECTORS MEETINGS MINUTES 2013 June 20 - 2014 June 12, TMs (Box-folder 018-006)
  President Cal Nichols.
- ANNUAL REPORT, UVA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY 2014 June, TMs (Box-folder 018-007)
- UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL AUXILIARY SNACK SHOP 1974-1998, TMs (Box-folder 019-001)
  The Snack Shop closed June 19, 1998.
- unidentified man and woman 1952, B&W 8"x10" photo (Box-folder 019-002)
  Both individuals are wearing military uniforms and standing next to an outside bell and structure explaining the use of a ship's bell. On the back of the photo is written, "Mrs. James A. Ward, Jr. 316 Eastbrook Drive Charlottesville, VA 22901
- Letter from Richard J. Ackart and Mrs. Joseph L. Vaughan to Mrs. Rutledge 1952 April 16, 1 TLs (Box-folder 019-003)
  The letter is inviting her to join the Hospital Circle.
- General Information and Statistics for the University of Virginia Hospital Auxiliary 1955 February 10, TMs (Box-folder 019-004)
- History of UVa Hospital Auxiliary by Angie (Mrs. Thomas) Chalmers 1955 March 29, TMs (Box-folder 019-005)
- History of the University Hospital and the UVa Hospital Auxiliary 1963, TMs (Box-folder 019-006)
- History of the Auxiliary 1968 August 5, TMs with annotations (Box-folder 019-007)
  Added note dated 1988 states records moved from Alderman Library to CMHSL
- Notes related to history of the Auxiliary 1968 August 5, AN (Box-folder 019-008)
- Letter from Elizabeth B. Gamble to Mrs. Jarman 19973 November 10, 1TLs, 1 ANs (Box-folder 019-009)
- Helen Baughman, John Harlan, Gay Kuhlthau, Janet Bonet, Connie Van Slyke, Ella Grigg ca. mid 1970s, B&W 7"x5" photo (Box-folder 019-010)
  John Harlan with 10 women, some identified
- Volunteer Handbook 1979 July, pamphlet (Box-folder 019-011)
- "Senior Hospital Voluneers Are 'Exceptional, Enthuastic'" in "The Daily Progress" 1979 September 4, newspaper clipping (Box-folder 019-012)
- Mrs. Mulholland to K. Respess for "To Whom It May Concern!" 1981 October 19, 1 TD (Box-folder 019-013)
  A partial history of the early beginnings of volunteer work at the University hospital.
- stationery showing St. Paul House and Alex Sawyer House post 1981, notecards, envelope, sheet with letterhead (Box-folder 019-014)
- Patient Handbook Inpatient Information range: 1982-1998, pamphlet (Box-folder 019-015)
- University of Virginia Hospital 1993, TD (Box-folder 019-016)
  Gives a brief history of the Auxiliary.
- "Volunteers lend a hand to hospitals'" in "The Daily Progress" 1994 January 24, newspaper clipping photocopy (Box-folder 019-017)
- "Volunteers cut, sew and stuff for children in hospital" in "SilverLinings" 1998 December, newspaper clipping photocopy (Box-folder 019-018)
- "Auxiliary Power'" in "The Daily Progress" 2008 January 20, newspaper clipping photocopy (Box-folder 019-019)
- The Susie Pegau Gift Shop n.d., metal plaque (Box-folder 019-016)
  Inside an envelope that states, "Guard this with your life!"